[music]
[музыка]
Hello my dears Today I will show
Приветик мои хорошие Сегодня я покажу
you the correct technique for performing the
вам правильную технику выполнения жима
bench press
штанги
this is a basic multi-component
лёжа это базовая много составное
exercise that should be performed not
упражнение которое должны выполнять не
only by men but also by women with the
только мужчины но и женщины при
classic exercise on a
классическом выполнении упражнений на
flat bench and with a wide hand position the
ровной скаме и с широкой постановкой рук
large and small pectoral muscles are worked out the
прорабатывается большая и Малая грудная
anterior deltoids and triceps let's
мышца передние дельты и трицепс
start with the correct technique for performing the
начнём с правильной техники выполнения
bench press lie down on a horizontal
жима лжа прилягте на горизонтальную
bench so that the bar
скамью таким образом чтобы штанга
is exactly above your
находилась точно над вашим
gaze the back of your head buttocks and shoulder blades are
взглядом затылок ягодицы и лопатки
pressed tightly to the bench legs Sherry shoulders and
плотно прижаты к скань ноги Шери плеч и
firmly rests on the floor the lower back bends a little
плотно упирается в пол поясница немного
you are not a powerlifter and you do
прогнуть с вами не пауэрлифтеры и
not need to pave here for greater
мостить здесь не нужно для большей
concentration on the pectoral muscles you can
концентрации на грудных мышцах можете
put your feet on the bench like this
поставить ноги на скамью таким образом
prov prot grab the bar with a wide
пров прот ухвати за штангу широким
closed grip adjust the position of your
закрытым хватом регулируйте постановку
hands so that when lowering the bar the angle in your
рук так чтобы при опускании грифа угол в
elbows is
локтях составлял
90 ° lower the bar from the stops and press it
90° спустите гриф с упоров и выжмите его
up Arms straight but not locked
Вверх Руки прямые но не заблокированные
elbows so that the load does not fall on the
локтях чтобы нагрузка не попадала на
joints and does not pass from the chest to the
суставы и не переходила от груди к
triceps this is the starting position taking a deep
трицепс это исходное положение глубоко
breath lower the bar to the lower part of the
вдохнув опустите гриф к нижней части
chest as soon as the bar
грудной клетки как только гриф
touches Lyuda strongly press the bar
дотронется до Люде сильно выжмите штангу
up and make a powerful exhalation through the mouth lower the
вверх и сделайте мощный выдох ртом
bar at a smooth and moderate
опускайте гриф в плавном и умеренном
pace and now about the wrong
темпе и теперь о не правильной
technique lower the bar to the lower part of the
техники опускайте гриф в нижнюю часть
chest and not under the chin or somewhere
груди а не под подбородок или куда-то
else grab the bar with a closed grip this is
ещё беритесь за гриф закрытым хватом это
much safer than an open grip
гораздо безопаснее чем открытый хват
lift the bar evenly without
поднимайте гриф ровно не
wobbling dumbbells or a lighter bar
шатаясь гантели или более лёгкого грифа
or even a
или даже буди
leg should rest firmly on the floor
ноги должны плотно упираться в пол
breathe correctly without holding your
дышите правильно не задерживая
breath If you are doing this
дыхание Если вы будете выполнять Это
exercise for the first time, then be sure to
упражнение в первый раз то обязательно
ask the trainer in the gym to check your
попросите тренера в зале проверить вашу
technique and in no case do not
технику и ни в коем случае не
hesitate to do this exercise
стесняйтесь выполнять Это упражнение
because it is supposedly for men because you
потому что оно якобы мужское ведь Вы
also want to have a beautiful and toned
тоже хотите иметь красивую и подтянутую
chest good luck to you and
грудь удачи вам и
[music]
[музыка]
bye N
пока N